I had no idea there were so many
different stalls for New Year's!
I've only ever been to smaller shrines,
so I've never seen anything like this before.
Shinozaki-san, look!
They've got a shooting game!
I'm so sorry! I was... not thinking...
No, please, don't worry about it!
I'm making such a fuss,
my kohai is going to think I'm childish.
She's making such a fuss...
Senpai's acting like a kid.
He
already
thought
it.
Do you think she's lost?
Maybe.
What's wrong?
Where are your parents?
I dunno...
I see.
You were very brave
to hang in there on your own.
I'll stay with you now, so don't worry.
Looks like she is lost.
That was really mature of you, Senpai.
Well, of course! I'm an adult, after all.
They've got a station for lost kids
at the reception desk, right?
Yeah! Let's go.
Look there, Yutaka-san.
Yeah.
They look like parents
with their child, don't they?!
I can see it... my cute little sister,
and her cute little daughter!
Would you two stop fussing? It's childish.
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#07 You Sure You Don't Want One?
Time to start a new year of work.
Good morning!
It's a pleasure to be
working with you again, Senpai!
Hearing you call me that makes me
feel like it's time to get back to work.
If you like it, I can call you that
whenever you like!
I have to say, New Year's went
by in the blink of an eye.
Considering you were a student last year,
it probably seems even faster.
I feel like...
the angle at which I'm looking up at
Shinozaki-san is different from usual...
Usual
Today
When I would see him before,
my head was around here.
Now I'm a little higher...
Could it be?
Have I gotten taller?!
Shinozaki-san.
Yes?
I'm a little different
than usual today. Can you tell?
She's different?
Her clothes and shoes are different,
but I don't think she'd ask
if it was something that obvious...
Standard practice is to check nails,
but those don't seem different...
You can't tell?
This scent...
That's it!
Did you switch to a different shampoo?
I did, but that's not what I meant!
I got it wrong! A pervert!
She'll think I'm a pervert!
Shinozaki-san...
you've been smelling my shampoo?
It's not like that, Senpai!
I swear, it wasn't anything untoward...
I'll need to be careful with my
shampoo choices going forward...
He seems really stumped.
I should give him an obvious hint.
Okay, here's a hint.
It's not my hair or anything in particular
like that, but more my body as a whole.
Your whole body?
Her whole... body...
I just told my kohai
to pay attention to my body!
That's what you're into, huh?
A pervert! He'll think I'm a pervert!
H-How about another hint?
L-Let's see...
Well, there's a big size difference between us.
That should make it pretty clear.
A size difference... Th-Then maybe...
You mean to say they've gotten even bigger?!
Did you figure it out?
It can't be that!
Well... I give up.
Okay, here's the answer.
It turns out...
Ta-da! I'm a little bit taller!
Now that you mention it,
you do seem a bit taller...
The boots... That explains it.
Yeah, you're wearing
boots for a change, after all.
My boots...
My boots... the soles...
the soles...
I'm just gonna sit here
for the rest of the day.
But maybe you did get a bit taller!
You don't need to humor me.
Well... Senpai...
I thought I was getting taller... Sulk...
Shinozaki-kun!
Yes?
I've got something I'd like you
to take care of today...
Public Relations
Ishiyama Satoshi
Well, Katase-san oversees my scheduling,
so you'll need to talk to her.
Don't be like that, Shinozaki-kun.
They do say, "when you're young,
you should tackle
as many challenges as you can!"
Pwease?
Making a cute face doesn't change the answer!
Unfortunately for you,
we're not in the habit of accepting challenges
that don't actually serve a purpose.
Katase-san!
Senpai.
I-I thought you were in a meeting...
Oh, so you asked Shinozaki-san about this
because you thought I wasn't around?
Catch you next time, Shinozaki-kun!
Ishiyama-kun never changes, does he?
An internal email?
Sender:
Ishiyama
To:
Me
Subject:
Our Discussion
Wanna do it in secret?
Wanna do it in secret?!
He doesn't give up!
Hiss!
Hiss! Hiss! Hiss! Hiss!
Please stop trying to assign work
directly to my subordinates!
But you wouldn't do it, Katase-san...
I never said I wouldn't!
But if you need something done,
you need to talk to me first,
so we can do things properly.
You mean it?!
In that case, I was wondering...
Katase-san really is quite the reliable senpai.
Okay.
I see...
This should be doable
if we adjust the schedule.
Yeah.
Really?! Thank you!
How'd your fortune turn out, Senpai?
Not telling.
My Tiny Senpai.
I'm still not used to being
here at night...
Whatcha doing?
My boss can seem to appear out of thin air.
D-Don't scare me like that!
I thought you were a ghost or something.
Sorry, sorry.
But why are you working late
by yourself if you're scared?
Were you really that busy?
Well...
Pwease?
Ishiyama-san in PR said
he needed this tomorrow...
Did he get approval from
your supervisor for this?
Hayakawa-san...
I know, I know!
He asked me right at the end of the day
and said there was no one else
he could turn to.
Even so, fundamentally speaking, you really
shouldn't accept assignments on your own.
Especially since you're new. Ask first.
Okay.
But I thought, if I could just
get it done in secret...
Still no.
That'd just mean he's taking advantage
of how nice you are, Hayakawa-san.
And speaking as a manager,
it's not nice at all!
You're completely right.
I'll have a word with Ishiyama-kun.
Sorry about all this...
Well, it's part of the job.
Um...
I really appreciate it.
What?! What's wrong?! You okay?!
Sorry...
It's just, having someone looking out
for me... made me so glad, y'know?
It's a real relief.
One second.
Here.
Thank you.
Have you eaten anything?
It was a rush job, so...
How much longer do you think it'll be?
I just need to submit it and I'll be done.
So fast!
If you've got time,
do you wanna grab something to eat?
You sure?
Consider it a little reward
for a hard worker who made a mistake.
How can he just say stuff like that...?
The entrance made it look like
modern residence,
but it's got an old fashioned Japanese style.
Kinda surprising, right?
Tempting to just space out, taking it in.
What?! Why did he just sit next to me?
Is this a move?
Is he pulling some kind of move on me?!
*Not really
thinking about it
Beers
Non-alcoholic
Drink Menu
What a big non-alcoholic selection!
I had no idea there was somewhere
like this so close to the office.
I noticed you almost never drink
when we have drinking parties,
so I thought you might enjoy it a bit more.
Are you trying to be the ideal guy right now?
What percentage of the office
has confessed to you before?
Not that many!
Didn't deny that he's been approached, though.
Manager... you never really talk about
your romantic history, do you?
No one really asks.
If I asked...
If I asked, would you tell me?
You wanna know?
I don't mean anything untoward by it!
Untoward how?
Is this just him? Is he just a ditz...?
Romance, huh...?
When I was younger, I didn't really
understand how it felt to like someone.
I tried dating quite a few times
up through college,
but in the end, I never really found love.
I think my life might just be one
with no romance to speak of.
Manager...
Is that why?
The thing is...
Nothing makes me happier than
cheering on someone else's love life.
I'm more curious about your
romantic history, Hayakawa-san!
M-Me...?
Now that reaction makes me curious!
Oho.
I thought I recognized that voice.
Yutaka-san!
Is your office around here?
Indeed. In the opposite direction of
the station, though, so it's a bit of a walk.
Some coworkers dragged me this way,
but I've never been one for big groups.
So I slipped out, but then realized...
It's lonely to be on your own!
So free-spirited!
That being the case,
would you mind if I joined you?
Go ahead.
If you'll excuse me...
Gimme pics of Shiorin!
Come on, what am I getting so anxious about?
Ask to your brother.
Besides, I don't have any.
All she did was sit
in an empty seat, normally...
Is that right?
It is.
Normally...
Chika-chan?
I think I'll sit here instead.
Just sit across the table
like a normal person!
Don't wanna.
I could see a wish for me to
sit here in those eyes.
Whose?!
Yours.
Well, you're wrong!
I saw it.
I guess... she didn't want to sit next to me.
Maybe I'll sit here, after all.
O-Onee-san...
In that case, I'll just sit over here.
You should sit here, Manager.
No, no, that's for you, Yutaka-san.
No, no...
What's with these two?
Hayakawa-san.
Chika-chan.
If I'm interrupting,
I'll head on home, so let me know.
Both of you sit down over there!
Okay.
Unbelievable...
You're really pouring it back, Chika-chan!
Are you a big drinker?
This is nonalcoholic!
I see. Yet, you're still red.
Oh, my!
Shut up!
My body feels heavy for some reason...
Is this sleep paralysis?
Li'l Bro. Gimme some Shiorin-senpai pics.
It's just you?! And could you not barge
into your brother's place on his day off?!
And... pictures of Senpai?
Correct. Shiorin's fluffiness
won't leave my mind.
I want to have a picture on hand
so I can air-fluff her at all times.
What kind of reason is that?!
And what are those hand movements?
Air-fluffing.
Yes, quite fluffy indeed.
Oh, that.
Anyway, I don't have any pics
of Senpai in the first place.
Then get some.
You should ask Hayakawa instead.
Gimme Shiorin pics.
No way.
Ask your brother.
Gimme
No way
Your manager said to task you.
Since when are you and my boss buddies?!
Though, you're right...
We could... show each other...
We could send each other
pictures of us wearing them!
We never did end up sending pics
of us wearing that loungewear...
And I can't deny I'd like to see that...
Yoink!
Sent!
What did you just send?!
Something from Shinozaki-san?
"I miss you on the weekend..."
"Could you please send a picture
so I can see you whenever I want?"
Wh-Wh-Where did this
come from all of a sudden?!
A-A-A-Am I dreaming?!
Am I still asleep right now?!
I should bathe first...
My phone!
Okay, I've got it back.
Great, it's already marked as read!
Read
Yay!
Senpai, it's a trick!
That was my sister! I didn't say that!
I'm so sorry!
My sister sent that!
You can ignore it.
His sister? That explains it.
She replied!
...You sure
you don't want one?
You sure you don't want one?
Manager
Ask for it!
Do it!
Could the peanut gallery pipe down?!
I'm so sorry!
My sister sent that!
You can ignore it.
...You sure
you don't want one?
I actually sent that...
And now if he says he wants a picture,
I should probably send one.
Sending a picture to Shinozaki-san.
Huh? All of a sudden...
I'm feeling really embarrassed!
Sending someone else a selfie like this...
Who even does that
unless you're going out already?!
"Senpai, I'm sorry."
He's gonna say he wants one!
"I'm busy, so I'll be back later!"
I'm partly relieved and partly frustrated!
Why am I so conflicted?!
You had better apologize
to Senpai for bothering her.
Consider it done!
From Shinozaki-san's sister?
Shiorin... Sorry about earlier.
Allow me to make amends...
My sleeping brother.
My brother drinking bubble tea.
My brother with a kitty.
My brother, running.
My brother, with sushi.
My brother, stretching.
Sh-She keeps sending pictures
of Shinozaki-san...!
My brother, writing.
My brother, in the bath.
Wait... in the bath...
W-W-Wouldn't that mean
Shinozaki-san is... n-na...
Naked?
Age 3.
What do you think you're doing?!
I never did hear back from Senpai yesterday.
Shinozaki-san.
Good morning, Shinozaki-san!
G-G-Good morning.
Um... I'm sorry about
how my sister acted yesterday.
It's quite all right.
And... about that picture you mentioned...
If it's not too much trouble,
I'd be really glad to receive one!
I said it! I actually said it!
There's no turning back now!
When I stop and think about it,
there's something embarrassing
about taking a picture of yourself.
After all this, am I stuck on the
"I changed my mind" path?!
Therefore...
why don't we take one together?
You and I?
Right!
That way, it won't be a picture of just me,
but a picture with you in it, too.
Senpai!
Great idea!
Manager?!
How long have you been there?!
Okay!
Shinozaki-kun,
get a little closer to Katase-san!
I-Is there a reason I need to get closer?!
There sure is!
Are you nervous, Shinozaki-san?
Yeah!
To be honest...
I'm kind of nervous, too.
Does that mean...?
Here we go!
Say cheese!
How's that?
Great! It turned out nicely.
I was actually in a pair shot with Senpai!
Huh? What're you all doing?
Hayakawa-san!
Since you're here,
you should take one with us, too!
What?
You get in here, too, Manager!
Me, too?
Does a five second timer sound good?
Yes!
Sure.
Wait, what are we doing?!
Hurry up, Hayakawa-san!
D-Smart Pharmaceuticals
Lil Bro
Sending pictures of
Senpai etc.
A picture of Senpai!
So, Li'l Bro, you finally have
a picture of Shiorin-senpai!
But...
What's this "etc." mean?
I-I want in on this! I feel left out!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar